Guide to the KUHT Records 1997-006
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- KUHT Production Files
  - Miscellaneous
    - Proposal Committee, 1987-1992 (Box 412, Folder 35)
    - Proposal Committee, 1993 (Box 412, Folder 36)
    - Public Affairs 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 37)
    - Public Affairs 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 38)
    - Prop-Com, 1993 (Box 412, Folder 39)
    - Series 1/2 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 40)
    - Series 1 hour, undated (Box 412, Folder 41)
    - Series 1 hour or more, undated (Box 412, Folder 42)
    - Television and Radio Code Brochures, undated (Box 412, Folder 43)
  - Public Relations Material
    - Annual Report, undated (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Auction - Art Preview, undated (Box 413, Folder 2-3)
    - Auction - Donor Benefits, undated (Box 413, Folder 4)
    - Auction - Donor File, undated (Box 413, Folder 5)
    - Auction - Flyers and Invitations, undated (Box 413, Folder 6)
    - Auction - Forms, undated (Box 413, Folder 7)
    - Auction - Miscellaneous Information, undated (Box 413, Folder 8)
    - Auction - Requests, undated (Box 413, Folder 9)
    - Auction - Thank you letters, undated (Box 413, Folder 10)
    - Award Show Programs, undated (Box 413, Folder 11)
    - Bradshaw Miscellaneous, undated (Box 413, Folder 12)
    - Channel 8 Gala, undated (Box 413, Folder 13)
    - Community Voice Program, undated (Box 413, Folder 14)
    - Flyers and Invitations, undated (Box 413, Folder 15)
    - Industrial Communications, undated (Box 413, Folder 16)
    - KUHF Material, undated (Box 413, Folder 17)
    - Membership Benefits and Requests, undated (Box 413, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 413, Folder 19-20)
    - Miscellaneous Log Forms, undated (Box 413, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Program Schedule, undated (Box 413, Folder 22)
    - Program Guides, undated (Box 413, Folder 23)
    - "Public Times", undated (Box 413, Folder 24)
    - Stationery, undated (Box 413, Folder 25)
    - Supporter "Thank You's", undated (Box 413, Folder 26)
    - Tape Labels, undated (Box 413, Folder 27)
    - Volunteer Newsletters, undated (Box 413, Folder 28)
    - Volunteer Sponsorship Material, undated (Box 413, Folder 29)
  - Special Projects
    - Aging, undated (Box 413, Folder 30)
    - AIDS Research, undated (Box 413, Folder 31)
    - Arts Alive, undated (Box 413, Folder 32)
    - Back to Work, undated (Box 413, Folder 33)
    - China Trip, 1990 (Box 413, Folder 34)
    - Computer Workshop, Summer 1993 (Box 414, Folder 1-2)
    - Equipment Order - Received Fiscal Year 82/83 (Box 414, Folder 3)
    - Fire Department, September 5, 1984, September 12, 1984 (Box 414, Folder 4)
    - Green Room #633 Magazine, May 31, 1982 (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - Green Room #634 Magazine, June 7, 1982 (Box 414, Folder 6)
    - Gubernatorial Debates, February 7 and 8, 1990 (Box 414, Folder 7-8)
    - Hispanic Politics - Betti Maldonado, Pending, 1991 (Box 414, Folder 9)
    - Know Your Rights, undated (Box 414, Folder 10)
    - Lombardi Budget, undated (Box 414, Folder 11)
    - Messiah/Baroque Rendition (Box 414, Folder 12)
    - Our Elderly at Stake, air 8:30 p.m., January 28, 1994 (Box 414, Folder 13)
    - Surviving Adolescence: It's Tough to Grow Up, undated (Box 414, Folder 14)
    - The Territory, undated (Box 414, Folder 15-17)
    - Turtle II Cost Accounting, 1985-1986 (Box 414, Folder 18)
    - Video-heads, undated (Box 414, Folder 19)
  - Video Files
    - Against All Odds and Achievers (Box 415, Folder 1)
    - Alabama-Coushatta Script "A Journey to the Sky" Final Draft (Box 415, Folder 2)
    - Alley Theater Press Release (Box 415, Folder 3-4)
    - Almanac (Box 415, Folder 5)
    - Almanac, 1989 (Box 415, Folder 6)
    - Almanac, Graphics (Box 415, Folder 7)
    - And the Beat Goes on... (Box 415, Folder 8-9)
    - And the Walls Came Tumbling Down (Box 415, Folder 10)
    - Armand Bayou: an Urban Wilderness (Box 415, Folder 11)
    - Arts Alive! (Box 415, Folder 12-15)
    - Auction, 1974 (Box 415, Folder 16)
    - Auction, 1976 (Box 415, Folder 17)
    - Auction, 1977 (Box 415, Folder 18)
    - Auction, 1978 (Box 415, Folder 19)
    - Auction, 1979 (Box 415, Folder 20)
    - Auction, 1980 (Box 415, Folder 21)
    - Auction, 1981 (Box 415, Folder 22)
    - Auction, 1982 (Box 416, Folder 1)
    - Auction, 1983 (Box 416, Folder 2)
    - Auction, 1984 (Box 416, Folder 3)
    - Auction, 1985 (Box 416, Folder 4)
    - Auction, 1986 (Box 416, Folder 5)
    - Auction, 1987 (Box 416, Folder 6)
    - Auction, 1988 (Box 416, Folder 7)
    - Auction, 1989 (Box 416, Folder 8)
    - Auction Advertising, 1990 (Box 416, Folder 9-12)
    - Auction Advertising - International Night, 1990 (Box 416, Folder 13)
    - Auction Advertising - Letters, 1990 (Box 416, Folder 14)
    - Auction Advertising - Local Newspaper, 1990 (Box 416, Folder 15)
    - Auction Advertising - Press Release "A Brief History of Auction", 1990 (Box 416, Folder 16)
    - Auction - August Showcase, Donor Forms, Log Liners, PG copy (Box 416, Folder 17)
    - Auction Bonanza Reports, 1988 (Box 417, Folder 1)
    - Auction Bonanza Reports, 1989 (Box 417, Folder 2)
    - Auction Bonanza Reports, 1990 (Box 417, Folder 3)
    - Auction House, Silent Auction, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 4)
    - Auction House, Silent Auction - Magazines, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 5)
    - Auction House, Silent Auction - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 6)
    - Auction House, Silent Auction - Newspapers, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 7)
    - Auction House, Silent Auction - Program Guides, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 8)
    - Auction House, Silent Auction - TV Guides, 1991 (Box 417, Folder 9)
    - Auction Memo - Scheduling/Scripting, 1981 (Box 417, Folder 10)
    - Auction Work (Box 417, Folder 11)
    - Baby Boomers and Beyond: Growing Old in Texas (Box 417, Folder 12)
    - Baby Bound (Box 417, Folder 13)
    - Baby, Maybe? (Box 417, Folder 14)
    - Back to Work (Box 417, Folder 15)
    - Ballet! What's the Point? (Box 417, Folder 16)
    - Bats (Box 417, Folder 17-18)
    - Bayou Bend: Collection & Gardens (Box 417, Folder 19)
    - Bean, Allen: Art of this Earth (Box 417, Folder 20-22)
    - Bean, Allen: Art of this Earth - Pictures (Box 417, Folder 23)
    - Beautiful People (Box 418, Folder 1)
    - Beyond Conflict Resolution (Box 418, Folder 2)
    - Big Thicket (Duplicate Copy) (Box 418, Folder 3)
    - Black Family Portrait (Box 418, Folder 4)
    - Black Gold Phoenix (Box 418, Folder 5)
    - Black History Month (Box 418, Folder 6)
    - Board of Regents/A Gift for the Future Script (Box 418, Folder 7)
    - Born on the Bayou (Box 418, Folder 8)
    - Boy Crying, Baby Crying (Box 418, Folder 9)
    - Bradshaw - Advertising, 1990 (Box 418, Folder 10)
    - Bradshaw - Eight Stages of Man (Box 418, Folder 11)
    - Bradshaw - Family DACS (Box 418, Folder 12-14)
    - Bradshaw - Specials, Clippings (Box 418, Folder 15)
    - Bradshaw - When you can't say no (Box 418, Folder 16)
    - The Brown Foundation (Box 418, Folder 17)
    - Buffalo, Canebrakes, and Old Texas Love Songs (Box 418, Folder 18)
    - Camera 8 (Box 418, Folder 19)
    - Cannibals (Box 418, Folder 20)
    - Capital Campaign (Box 418, Folder 21)
    - CARE/Melcher Project (Box 418, Folder 22-25)
    - Carter-Menil Human Rights Award, 1991 (Box 419, Folder 1)
    - Carter-Menil Human Rights Award - Rothko Chapel Awards (Box 419, Folder 2)
    - Center Stage (Box 419, Folder 3-4)
    - Center Stage - Distribution (Box 419, Folder 5)
    - Center Stage - Event (Box 419, Folder 6)
    - Center Stage - Funding (Box 419, Folder 7)
    - Center Stage - Old Secrets (Box 419, Folder 8)
    - Center Stage - Old Secrets, Publicity, etc. (Box 419, Folder 9)
    - Center Stage - Parts, 1993 (Box 419, Folder 10)
    - Center Stage - Script Release Agreements (Box 419, Folder 11)
    - Center Stage - Story Ideas/Treatments (Box 419, Folder 12)
    - Challenge of Grief (Box 419, Folder 13)
    - Challenge of Grief: AIDS and Seven Choices (Box 419, Folder 14)
    - Challenge of Grief/SECA/1-31-93-1900-2000-1c (Box 419, Folder 15)
    - Chamical People (Box 419, Folder 16)
    - Child Abuse - Award (Box 419, Folder 17)
    - Child Abuse - Breaking the Cycle (Box 419, Folder 18)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Agreement, Correspondence, Reference Material (Box 419, Folder 19)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Cassette Purchases (Box 419, Folder 20)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Local Press (Box 419, Folder 21)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Mailing Lists (Box 419, Folder 22)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Marketing Material (Box 419, Folder 23)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Marketing and Promotion Plans (Box 419, Folder 24)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Miscellaneous (Box 419, Folder 25-27)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Narration (Box 419, Folder 28)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Photos, Film, Slides (Box 420, Folder 1)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Press Release (Box 420, Folder 2)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Press Release Award (Box 420, Folder 3)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Print Ad (Box 420, Folder 4)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Production Notes (Box 420, Folder 5)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Program Guides (Box 420, Folder 6)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Research, Development Correspondence (Box 420, Folder 7)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Response Letters (Box 420, Folder 8)
    - Child Abuse, the Perfect Crime - Scripts, Changes, Edits (Box 420, Folder 9)
    - Child Abuse Programs and Network Road Blocks (Box 420, Folder 10)
    - Child Abuse Special (Box 420, Folder 11)
    - Child at Risk files
      Film and documentation related to "Child at Risk" (Box 420, Folders 12-37 and Box 421, Folders 1-45) is closed to research for reasons of privacy and confidentiality.
    - Children's Event 40th Anniversary (Box 421, Folder 46)
    - Christmas Festival of Harps (Box 421, Folder 47)
    - City Scene (Box 421, Folder 48)
    - Community (Box 421, Folder 49-50)
    - Community - Beta Dub Tape List (Box 421, Folder 51)
    - Community - Black (Box 421, Folder 52)
    - Community - Bull Riders (Box 421, Folder 53)
    - Community - Calendar (Box 421, Folder 54)
    - Community - Debut Press Release (Box 422, Folder 1)
    - Community - Distribution (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Community - Duties (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Community - Episode #114, April 19, 1991 (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Community - Episode #301, Treasures (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - Community - Episode #302, Children, 25:48 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Community - Episode #303, Dogs, 25:44 (Box 422, Folder 7)
    - Community - Episode #304, Music, 25:04 (Box 422, Folder 8)
    - Community - Episode #305, History, 26:02 (Box 422, Folder 9)
    - Community - Episode #306, Artists, 26:34 (Box 422, Folder 10)
    - Community - Episode #307, 20:03 (Box 422, Folder 11)
    - Community - Episode #308, Doctors, 24:04 (Box 422, Folder 12)
    - Community - Episode #309, Writers Part 1 (Box 422, Folder 13)
    - Community - Episode #311, Writers Part 2 (Box 422, Folder 14)
    - Community - Episode #311, Writers Theme Show, December 29, 1992 (Box 422, Folder 15)
    - Community - Episode #312, New Season Show (Box 422, Folder 16)
    - Community - Episode #313, January 12, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 17)
    - Community - Episode #314, January 19, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 18)
    - Community - Episode #315, January 26, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 19)
    - Community - Episode #316, February 2, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 20)
    - Community - Episode #317, February 9, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 21)
    - Community - Episode #318, February 16, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 22)
    - Community - Episode #319, February 23, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 23)
    - Community - Episode #320, March 2, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 24)
    - Community - Episode #321, March 9, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 25)
    - Community - Episode #322, March 23, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 26)
    - Community - Episode #323, March 30, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 27)
    - Community - Episode #324, April 6, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 28)
    - Community - Episode #325, April 13, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 29)
    - Community - Episode #326, April 20, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 30)
    - Community - Episode #327, April 27, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 31)
    - Community - Episode #328, May 4, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 32)
    - Community - Episode #329, May 11, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 33)
    - Community - Episode #330, May 18, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 34)
    - Community - Episode #331, May 25, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 35)
    - Community - Episode #332, June 1, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 36)
    - Community - Episode #333, June 8, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 37)
    - Community - Episode #334, June 22, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 38)
    - Community - Episode #335, June 24, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 39)
    - Community - Episode #336, June 15, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 40)
    - Community - Episode #337, July 6, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 41)
    - Community - Episode #338, July 6, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 42)
    - Community - Episode #339-T, July 20, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 43)
    - Community - Episode #340-T, July 27, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 44)
    - Community - Episode #341, August 3, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 45)
    - Community - Episode #342, August 10, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 46)
    - Community - Episode #343, August 17, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 47)
    - Community - Episode #344, August 24, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 48)
    - Community - Episode #345, August 31, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 49)
    - Community - Episode #346, September 7, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 50)
    - Community - Episode #347, September 14, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 51)
    - Community - Episode #348, September 21, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 52)
    - Community - Episode #349, September 28, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 53)
    - Community - Episode #350-R, October 5, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 54)
    - Community - Episode #351-R, October 12, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 55)
    - Community - Episode #352-R, October 19, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 56)
    - Community - Episode #353-R, October 26, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 57)
    - Community - Episode #354, November 2, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 58)
    - Community - Episode #355, November 9, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 59)
    - Community - Episode #356, November 16, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 60)
    - Community - Episode #357, November 23, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 61)
    - Community - Episode #358, November 30, 1993 (Box 422, Folder 62)
    - Community - Episode #401, January 4, 1994 (Box 422, Folder 63)
    - Community - Episode #402, January 11, 1994 (Box 422, Folder 64)
    - Community - Episode #403, January 18, 1994 (Box 422, Folder 65)
    - Community - Episode #404, January 25, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 1)
    - Community - Episode #405, February 1, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 2)
    - Community - Episode #406, February 8, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 3)
    - Community - Episode #407, February 15, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 4)
    - Community - Episode #408, February 15, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 5)
    - Community - Episode #409, March 1, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 6)
    - Community - Episode #410, March 15, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 7)
    - Community - Episode #411, March 22, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 8)
    - Community - Episode #412, March 29, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 9)
    - Community - Episode #413, April 15, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 10)
    - Community - Episode #414, April 12, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 11)
    - Community - Episode #415, April 19, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 12)
    - Community - Episode #501, April 26, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 13)
    - Community - Episode #502, May 3, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 14)
    - Community - Episode #503, May 10, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 15)
    - Community - Episode #504, May 17, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 16)
    - Community - Episode #505, May 24, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 17)
    - Community - Episode #506, May 31, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 18)
    - Community - Episode #507, June 7, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 19)
    - Community - Episode #508, June 14, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 20)
    - Community - Episode #509, June 21, 1994 (Box 423, Folder 21)
    - Community - Hewey, Todd (Box 423, Folder 22)
    - Community - Hispanic (Box 423, Folder 23)
    - Community - Individual (Box 423, Folder 24)
    - Community - Maldonado, Betti (Box 423, Folder 25)
    - Community - Miscellaneous (Box 423, Folder 26)
    - Community - Miscellaneous, Visuals, Music Cue Sheets, Local Reports (Box 423, Folder 27)
    - Community - Nureyev (Box 423, Folder 28)
    - Community - Paris, Wendy (Box 423, Folder 29)
    - Community - Phone #3XX (Box 423, Folder 30)
    - Community - Proposals (Box 423, Folder 31)
    - Community - Publicity (Box 423, Folder 32)
    - Community - Season 1, Schedule (Box 423, Folder 33)
    - Community - Season 2, Schedule (Box 423, Folder 34)
    - Community - Season 3 (Box 423, Folder 35)
    - Community - Season 3, Davenport, John (Box 423, Folder 36)
    - Community - Season 4, Producer Reports (Box 423, Folder 37)
    - Community - Season 4, Scripts (Box 423, Folder 38)
    - Community - Season 4, Stand-up Scripts (Box 423, Folder 39)
    - Community - Segments (Box 424, Folder 1)
    - Community - Space (Box 424, Folder 2)
    - Community - Stages (Box 424, Folder 3)
    - Community - Story (Box 424, Folder 4)
    - Community - Theme Show (Box 424, Folder 5)
    - Community - Tuts, Phantom (Box 424, Folder 6)
    - Community - Viewer Calls (Box 424, Folder 7)
    - Community - Whitt, Margo (Box 424, Folder 8)
    - Community - Writers, 1991-1992 (Box 424, Folder 9)
    - Community - Yeager (Box 424, Folder 10)
    - Cozins, "Men" Transcript (Box 424, Folder 11-12)
    - Cultural Unit, Personnel (Box 424, Folder 13)
    - DAC, April 1987 (Box 424, Folder 14)
    - "Dead Ahead," Grateful Dead Pledge Drive (Box 424, Folder 15)
    - Doctor Greek Soul (Box 424, Folder 16)
    - Dollars and Sense (Box 424, Folder 17)
    - Drowning in Debt (Box 424, Folder 18)
    - Duets for Cannibals (Box 424, Folder 19-20)
    - Dumped in the Promised Land (Box 424, Folder 21)
    - Dutch Co-Production (Box 424, Folder 22)
    - Eagle and the Lone Star (Box 424, Folder 23)
    - Elderly at Stake (Box 424, Folder 24)
    - Escape from Failure (Box 424, Folder 25)
    - Evolution of a Classic, video (Box 424, Folder 26)
    - Faulk, John Henry, Down on the Farm (Box 424, Folder 27)
    - Festival, 1985 (Box 425, Folder 1-2)
    - Festival - Print Advertising, 1986 (Box 425, Folder 3)
    - Festival, 1987 (Box 425, Folder 4)
    - Festival, 1988 (Box 425, Folder 5)
    - Festival, 1989 (Box 425, Folder 6)
    - Festival - Miscellaneous (Box 425, Folder 7)
    - Festival - Restored 477-81 (Box 425, Folder 8)
    - Festival - Restored 9983-84 (Box 425, Folder 9-11)
    - Financial Fraud: A Special Report (Box 425, Folder 12)
    - Fire in the East (Box 425, Folder 13)
    - First Hand with Cindy Cochran (Box 425, Folder 14)
    - Fishing Troubled Waters (Box 425, Folder 15)
    - Floyd/Wade (Box 425, Folder 16)
    - "Focus on Success," Women's Show (Box 425, Folder 17)
    - Ford, Margaret Snow (Box 425, Folder 18)
    - For Pets' Sake (Box 425, Folder 19)
    - Forty Pounds of Granite: A Ton of Hope (Box 425, Folder 20)
    - Fotofest (Box 425, Folder 21)
    - Fresh Paint - Roberta Hammond (Box 425, Folder 22)
    - The Friday Local, 1978 (Box 425, Folder 23)
    - A Friend Like Patty (Box 425, Folder 24)
    - From the Darkest Corner (Box 425, Folder 25)
    - Fulgnum, Robert (Box 425, Folder 26)
    - Ghosts: B-17, Tora, Wasp (Box 425, Folder 27-29)
    - Ghosts: Florida (Box 426, Folder 1)
    - Ghosts: Honor Squadron - Paper Logs of All Shoots, 459th Reunion Copy (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - Ghosts: Honor Squadron - Paper Logs of All Shoots, WH Copy, 1991-1994 (Box 426, Folder 3-5)
    - Ghosts: Honor Squadron - Paper Logs of All Shoots, Seattle Copy (Box 426, Folder 6)
    - Ghosts: WH, 1993 (Box 426, Folder 7-8)
    - Ghost Stories (Box 426, Folder 9)
    - Gift of Learning (Box 426, Folder 10)
    - Gifted Children: An Untapped Resource (Box 426, Folder 11)
    - Governor's Conference 2000 on Education Goals Nationwide (Box 426, Folder 12)
    - The Great Persuaders (Box 426, Folder 13)
    - Greener Pastures (Box 426, Folder 14)
    - Green Room (Box 426, Folder 15)
    - Henry VIII (Box 426, Folder 16)
    - Hexameron: A Piano Spectacular (Box 426, Folder 17)
    - Higher Learning (Box 426, Folder 18)
    - Home Brew (Box 426, Folder 19-20)
    - Home Brew: News (Box 426, Folder 21)
    - The Home Brewery - "Everything Wants to be Beer" (Box 426, Folder 22)
    - Honza K. - Jan Kristofori (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - House Calls (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - House Calls, 1992 (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - Houston After Dark: The Sounds of Houston (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - Houston Ballet (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - Houston Chronicle (Box 427, Folder 6)
    - Houston Homeless (Box 427, Folder 7)
    - Houston Justice for Children (Box 427, Folder 8)
    - Houston Mayoral Debates (Box 427, Folder 9)
    - Houston Public Television - Dub/Time Request (Box 427, Folder 10)
    - Houston Talk Shows - Television (Box 427, Folder 11)
    - Houston Weekly (Box 427, Folder 12)
    - HOV: Music Stop Segments (Box 427, Folder 13)
    - HOV: Stealth Show (Box 427, Folder 14)
    - How to be a Financially Secure Woman (Box 427, Folder 15)
    - HPD: The People and the Police (Box 427, Folder 16)
    - HPD: Publicity Originals (Box 427, Folder 17)
    - Hurricane in a Double Wide & The Pear Tree (Box 427, Folder 18)
    - Images of America (Box 427, Folder 19)
    - Impressions of Jamaica (Box 427, Folder 20)
    - In Black and White (Box 427, Folder 21)
    - Independent Living (Box 427, Folder 22)
    - In Search of Shakespeare (Box 427, Folder 23)
    - Is Teenager a Disease or What, Girls? (Box 427, Folder 24)
    - Intermezzo (Box 427, Folder 25-26)
    - In the Name of God: National Awards Release (Box 427, Folder 27)
    - InterChange (Box 427, Folder 28)
    - International Festival, 1995 (Box 427, Folder 29)
    - JD's Journal, 1992 (Box 427, Folder 30)
    - JD's Journal - Local Production (Box 427, Folder 31)
    - JD's Journal/SECA - Sundays, January 3, 1993 (Box 427, Folder 32)
    - Johnston, Gearoge & Breslou (Box 427, Folder 33)
    - Journey to the Sky (Box 428, Folder 1-2)
    - The Joy Gay Report (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - J.R. League: Homeless in Houston - Tape Logs (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - Killer Bees (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - Kinkos (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - Know Your Rights (Box 428, Folder 7)
    - KUHF - Program/Radio Guides (Box 428, Folder 8-12)
    - KUHT - History Documentary Scripts (Box 428, Folder 13)
    - KUHT - Promotions, TV (Box 428, Folder 14)
    - Last Stand of the Buffalo (Box 428, Folder 15)
    - Lawyer to Layman (Box 428, Folder 16)
    - Life Along the Channel (Box 428, Folder 17-18)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Accounts (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - Live at the Woodlands - August 28, Woodlands (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Backstage, Peace Concert, TV Sun. (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Blues Information (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Budget (Box 429, Folder 5-6)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Check Request (Box 429, Folder 7)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Chronicle (Box 429, Folder 8)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Contract, Phone Number (Box 429, Folder 9)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Contracts (Box 429, Folder 10)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Correspondence (Box 429, Folder 11-12)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Credits, Blues, New Orleans (Box 429, Folder 13)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Crew (Box 429, Folder 14)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Cue Sheets (Box 429, Folder 15)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Description of Woodlands (Box 429, Folder 16)
    - Live at the Woodlands - Edit Logs, Notes (Box 429, Folder 17)